magazine-agent.com 2018-11-15

# Magazine-Agent.com | Privacy Policy

### About this Site

Effective Date of Policy: June 1st, 2015 - Previous Policy

This site is operated by [Contrix Inc.](http://www.contrix.com/), on behalf of Magazine-Agent.com, hereinafter all collectively referred to as the “Site.” By visiting the Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

### Information Collected from All Visitors

The Site may collect certain profile information from its users (including but not limited to browser information, IP address, and general demographic information, pages visited, time spent on pages and which site, if any, the user visited prior to arriving at the Site) in order to improve our content, product offerings, and promotional and marketing efforts. Our company also may use profile information to create aggregate reports about its users. The above information may be collected using cookies, server logs, and third party tracking solutions. In addition to the forgoing, the Site may collect and maintain any information that you directly provide while visiting the Site. Except as specifically stated herein, we have not granted any third party the right to share your information with others.

### Additional Information Collected from Registered Users and Customers

In order to fulfill customer orders and enhance user experience, the Site collects certain specific personally identifiable information that its customers and registered users provide when visiting the Site, such as their first and last name, their home or other physical address including their street name and the name of their city or town, their email address, their telephone number, and their credit card information (none of the above-listed types of personally identifiable information will be collected unless provided directly by the user). Such information is shared with contracted third-parties in order to fill orders accurately and promptly, provide customer service assistance, improve your shopping service, and improve the content of the Site generally so that we may better meet our users' needs. We may also provide the personally identifiable information (except email and credit card information) we collect from our users to other businesses and companies that sell a wide variety of products and services that we believe will be of interest to our customers. Because we respect the privacy of our customers and visitors, you can request that we not share your personally identifiable information with these other businesses and companies by[changing your privacy preferences by logging in to your account](https://manage.magazine-agent.com/). **Except as specifically set forth in this privacy policy, we will never share your email address or credit card information with third-parties**. Furthermore (as noted above), except as specifically stated herein, we have not granted any third party the right to share your information with others.

### Multiple Businesses with Common Systems

In addition to the Site, Contrix Inc. (1) may operate sites for publishing companies and (2) operate other proprietary sites which act as third party resellers of discount magazine subscriptions, collectively "Other Sites". Contrix may store information collected from the Site and information collected from Other Sites in the same systems and in turn Contrix may analyze any and all information from both the Site and Other Sites in the aggregate. 

### Setting Communication Preferences

The Site communicate with our customers through email. Such communications are broken out into the following two categories:

  *  **Order Related Communications** – The Site utilizes email to communicate with our customers about their order. These communications include order confirmation emails sent at the time of your order and customer service emails which address ongoing concerns about your order, including but not limited, to payments issues, address changes, renewal preferences, and subscription expiration.
  *  **Marketing Communications** – The Site utilized email to communicate offers and announce features that we believe will be of interest to our customers. These promotional emails are highly targeted and are designed to deliver relevant information about our various products and services. 

If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your email preferences by logging into our Account Manager. Note that to the extent your opting out of communications precludes you from receiving updates to our Terms & Conditions and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of the Site, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes. Additionally, please note that even if you unsubscribe from our marketing emails, the Site will continue to send you important transactional correspondence about your subscriptions such as any communications regarding financial transactions as well as responded via email to any customer service tickets you may create about an order.

### Use of Order Information with Third Parties

When you place an order for a magazine, the Site sends your personal information, including name, address, credit card information and the titles you ordered to its fulfillment partners. Fulfillment partners may only use this information to fulfill, bill, and service your order. They have agreed not to sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information, or to use this information for any secondary purpose, including marketing.top

### Contractual Relationships

We provide your information to our third party service vendors with whom we have contractual relationships for the purpose of servicing our processing of your order. These vendors provide various services on our behalf such as customer service, billing and fulfillment. These vendors have agreed not to sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information or to use your information for any secondary purpose.top

### Exceptional Circumstances

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary, with respect to all users of our Site, we reserve the right to disclose any content, records, or electronic communication of any kind (including personal information or private electronic communication transmitted on our site): (i) to satisfy any law, regulation, or government request; (ii) if such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate the Site; or (iii) to protect the rights or property of Magazine-Agent.com or its users, sponsors, providers, licensors, or merchants. The Site also reserves the right to reject any order or to request additional information from any customer.top

### Business Transfers

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell corporate assets. Customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred in this type of transaction, and notwithstanding anything to the contrary, it is possible that your information may be transferred if we enter such a transaction. Additionally, if the Site is acquired, if substantially all of our are acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, then notwithstanding anything to the contrary, the customer information that we collect (including personally identifiable information) may be transferred to or acquired by a third party, and that third party may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.top

### Security

The information regarding your order is always sent in encrypted format in order to protect against accidental disclosure. As an added safeguard, your credit card information is encrypted on our servers.top

### Correcting/Updating Personal Information

If you want to change your personal information (such as your address or credit card number) you can do so by accessing our[online account manager](http://https//manage.magazine-agent.com/) or by calling customer service at (888) 590-0030.top

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the site by identifying them as changes to our previous privacy policy. We will identify those changes for at least 60 days so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.top

### Questions

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact our Privacy Department by using our online contact form, or by mailing us at the address below and including a mailing address for our response.

 **Contrix, Inc.  
Privacy Department  
110 E 42nd St  
Suite 1311  
New York, NY 10017**

top

### Publishers

When you order a magazine, we forward the name of the recipient and the postal address to which the magazine is to be delivered to the applicable magazine publisher for fulfillment. This information will be governed by the privacy policy of the magazine publishers for the titles you have chosen to receive. No other personally identifiable information is shared with the publisher of the magazine ordered.top
